<caseStudy>
           <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Evokelabs Flash Portfolios 2003 - 2013</heading>            
                <client>Evokelabs</client>            
                <technology>Flash, AS2, AS3, Flex, Papervision, 3d</technology>            
                <brief>Celebrating 15+ years of Evokelabs and remembering the now gone SWF flash format.</brief>            
                <desc>                  
                </desc>
            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/evokelabs.jpg</thumb>  

                <video>img/casestudies/evokelabs-front.mp4</video> 
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/Flashsites-Evokelabs.mp4</main-video>  
            
                <link></link>  
        </caseStudyItem>
        <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>TikTok Collection 2021 - 2022</heading>            
                <client>Akcelo &amp; TikTok Australia/NZ + TikTok Canada </client>            
                <technology>HTML, CSS, Foundation for Email, Mailchimp</technology>            
                <brief>eDM development and CRM integration for TikTok Australia/NZ + TikTok Canada.</brief>            
                <desc>                  
                </desc>
            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/tiktok.jpg</thumb>  

                <video>img/casestudies/tiktok.mp4</video> 
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/TikTok-EL.mp4</main-video>  
            
                <link></link>  
        </caseStudyItem>
       
              
          <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Petculture eDMs</heading>            
                <client>Akcelo &amp; Petculture</client>            
                <technology>HTML, CSS, Foundation for Email, Klaviyo</technology>            
                <brief>eDM development and CRM integration for Petculture.</brief>            
                <desc>                  
                </desc>
            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/petculture.jpg</thumb>  

                <video>img/casestudies/petculture.mp4</video> 
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/petculture-el.mp4</main-video>  
            
                <link></link>  
        </caseStudyItem>

          <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Wisemans Surf Lodge eDMs</heading>            
                <client>Akcelo &amp; Wisemans Surf Lodge</client>            
                <technology>HTML, CSS, Foundation for Email, Hubspot</technology>            
                <brief>eDM development and CRM integration for Wisemans Surf.</brief>            
                <desc>                  
                </desc>
            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/wiseman.jpg</thumb>  

                <video>img/casestudies/wiseman.mp4</video> 
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/Wiseman-EL.mp4</main-video>  
            
                <link></link>  
        </caseStudyItem>


  <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Flexigroup</heading>            
                <client>Frontend Developer &amp; Digital Designer</client>            
                <technology>HTML, CSS, Adobe, Figma, Foundation for Email</technology>            
                <brief>Video presentation on the time I spent at Flexigroup as their lead eDM developer &amp; digital designer.</brief>            
                <desc>                  
                </desc>
            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/flexigroup1.jpg</thumb> 

                <video>img/casestudies/Flexigroup-Front.mp4</video> 
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/Flexigroup.mp4</main-video>  
            
                <link></link>  
        </caseStudyItem>

          <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Hyland Communication Agency</heading>            
                <client>Wordpress Specialist &amp; HTML5 Banner Designer</client>            
                <technology>Wordpress, CSS, PHP, Animate CC, Doubleclick</technology>            
                <brief>Video presentation on the works I've done for Hyland Communication Agency as their digital freelancer.</brief>            
                <desc> 
                </desc>
            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/hyland1.jpg</thumb> 

                <video>img/casestudies/Hyland-Front.mp4</video> 
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/Hyland.mp4</main-video>  
            
                <link>http:///www.siecap.com.au</link>  
        </caseStudyItem>
                           
        <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Unlearn Campaign Banner Suite</heading>            
                <client>University of Sydney</client>            
                <technology>Photoshop CC, Animate CC, HTML, JS, Doubleclick</technology>            
                <brief>The Unlearn Campaign is a 30+ HTML5 banner suite designed and developed for USYD.</brief>            
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[
              <p>The basis of UNSW’s “Unlearn” campaign was to showcase the university’s innovative discoveries to the world. While the print and TV deliverables were in production, I was responsible for the digital execution of the campaign - converting their rich media creatives into light-weight HTML5 banners. These banners were hosted on the DoubleClick platform for mobile and desktop ad spaces.</p>
                ]]>
                </desc>            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/university1.jpg</thumb> 
                <video>img/casestudies/14-University.mp4</video> 
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/university.mp4</main-video>              
                <link></link>  
        </caseStudyItem> 

        <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Richards Rose Website</heading>            
                <client>Richards Rose</client>            
                <technology>HTML5, CSS, JS, Wordpress</technology>            
                <brief>Richards Rose is a customisable Wordpress build developed for an independent Sydney agency.</brief>            
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[
                
                <p>When Richards Rose announced its independence from AJF Partnership, they needed a new web presence to supplement their relaunch. I was contracted to build their new agency site since I already had a good relationship & proven track record with AJF Partnership/Richards Rose. I was given a little more than a wireframe & a PSD design file, and with it I was able to turn around a fully fledged responsive and customisable Wordpress site within two weeks.</p> 
                
                <p>This site was tailored to be easily editable by the staff at Richards Rose, using user-friendly plugins and custom CSS. The agency’s homepage has gone through some updates, client changes and additions since its inception, but it has all been built on the Wordpress foundation that I provided.</p>

                ]]>
                </desc>            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/richardrosewebsite1.jpg, img/casestudies/richardrosewebsite2.jpg, img/casestudies/richardrosewebsite3.jpg</thumb> 
                <video>img/casestudies/01-richardrose.mp4</video>   
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/richardsrose.mp4</main-video>              
                <link>http://www.richardsrose.com.au</link>  
        </caseStudyItem>

        <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Stan HTML5 Banner Suite</heading>            
                <client>Stan &amp; Richards Rose</client>            
                <technology>Animate CC</technology>            
                <brief>Stan Banner Suite is a Flash template build for StreamCo that exports dynamic HTML5 banners.</brief>            
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[
                
                <p>I was contracted by Richards Rose to produce HTML5 banners for the Australian streaming company Stan, which was briefed to have the titles, the show logo, the hero image and the accompanied video to be all dynamically alterable. Originally, it was designed with HTML5 and GSAP in mind, but given the complexity of the animations and the masking effects, it was rebuilt using the robust features found in Animate CC.</p> 
                
                <p>Lightweight, customisable and with the ability to export to HTML5 -  these banners were built in a way so any team member with even the most modest experience in Animate CC could replace any element with minimal fuss, creating a customisable dynamic experience without the headaches.</p>


                ]]>
                </desc>
            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/stan1.jpg, img/casestudies/stan2.jpg, img/casestudies/stan3.jpg </thumb> 
                <video>img/casestudies/02-StanBanners.mp4</video>
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/stan.mp4</main-video>     
            
                <link></link>  
        </caseStudyItem> 

        <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Richards Rose HTML5 Banner Suite</heading>            
                <client>Richards Rose &amp; and many accounts</client>            
                <technology>HTML5, CSS, JS, GSAP, Animate CC</technology>            
                <brief>A collection of HTML5 banners built for Richards Rose and their clients using Animate / hand-coded HTML5.</brief>            
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[
                
               <p>I specialised in creating Flash banners for advertising agencies early in my career. But when Google killed Flash by implementing a “click-to-play“ feature within Chrome in 2015, it destroyed the Flash banner industry overnight. Fortunately, my skills in animation and AS2 development could be transferred into HTML5 technologies. AJF Partnership and Richards Rose were generous enough to allow me to transition from creating SWF banners, into using HTML5. Below is the banner suite I have made during my freelance career with Richards Rose.</p>

                <p>Typically, my banners are either built using Animate CC and exported to CanvasJS, or hand coded using traditional front end techniques using HTML5, CSS, JS and GSAP. I still find banner production to be enjoyable, challenging and rewarding, and while I’ll probably never make another SWF banner again, the benefits of correctly using HTML5 outweigh the limitations of SWF.</p>


                ]]>
                </desc>
            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/richardbanners1.jpg, img/casestudies/richardbanners2.jpg, img/casestudies/richardbanners3.jpg</thumb> 

                <video>img/casestudies/03-BannerBuilds.mp4</video>   
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/richardbanners.mp4</main-video>  
                <link></link>  
        </caseStudyItem>

        <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Richards Rose Motion Build Suite</heading>            
                <client>Richards Rose &amp; and many accounts</client>            
                <technology>Photoshop CC, After Effects CC</technology>            
                <brief>A collection of motion builds for Richards Rose and their clients built with Adobe After Effects.</brief>            
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[
                
                <p>With impressive codecs, the HTML5 video tag, and faster internet connections, motion design has become more relevant for advertising, social media pages and digital displays than the early days of HTML4 and SWF. I have a strong background in animation and After Effects, and so whenever Richards Rose needed a motion designer to convert their Photoshop storyboards into a deliverable video, I always accepted their freelance work if I was available.</p>
                
                <p>Each motion piece I produced was built around their given specs, converting their flat PSD artboards into deliverable MP4s that are engaging, accessible and conveyed a memorable message. These designs are then exported to be shown on public displays, social media pages or TVCs. Below is some of the motion suite I have made during my freelance career with Richards Rose.</p>


                ]]>
                </desc>
            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/richardmotion1.jpg, img/casestudies/richardmotion2.jpg, img/casestudies/richardmotion3.jpg</thumb> 
                <video>img/casestudies/04-motionbuilds.mp4</video>   
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/richardsmotion.mp4</main-video>  
                <link></link>  
        </caseStudyItem>

        <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>DJ Ravine - Brand Identity</heading>            
                <client>DJ Ravine</client>            
                <technology>Illustrator CC, Photoshop CC, Social Media</technology>            
                <brief>Logo creation and brand identity created for world renowned YouTuber and music producer, DJ Ravine.  </brief>            
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[

                <p>Dj Ravine is a world renown YouTuber, music producer and personal friend. With 500,000 subscribers earned through his videos, he didn’t yet have a brand identity that reflected his online presence.</p>
                
                <p>Following design treads found in the electronic music industry and other online personalities, I designed an original logo and manipulated a custom font to create his new brand, as well as producing video overlays, social media backgrounds and 3D animations that are used across his social media accounts.</p>
                
                <p>This brand identity, which was originally drawn in my stretchbook, is now found in circulated flyers, stickers, display LEDs, and 3d printed accessories - supplementing his real life identity with a recognisable graphical brand.</p>


                ]]>
                </desc>            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/ravine1.jpg, img/casestudies/ravine2.jpg, img/casestudies/ravine3.jpg</thumb> 
                <video>img/casestudies/09-Ravine.mp4</video>   
                <link></link> 
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/ravine.mp4</main-video> 
        </caseStudyItem>                

        <caseStudyItem>
                <heading>Let It Go with Crystal Maiden</heading>
                <client>Evokelabs</client>
                <technology>3dsmax, Motion, Steam Workshop, Audio</technology>
                <brief>"Let It Go" with Crystal Maiden is a digital recreation of the Frozen's "Let It Go" with 1.4+ million views on YouTube.</brief>
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[
              <p>"Let It Go" with Crystal Maiden is an original 3d cinematic parody of "Let It Go" from Frozen. The video was produced and animated by myself, sung by Janice Pan, and was produced between three to six months. It features a large number of digital effects including; character rigging, particle effects, animation and an original score that was released as a 5 minute YouTube short.</p>

                <p>A custom cosmetic piece was also crafted for this character which supplemented the original launch of this video. This was created for the Steam Workshop as a potential revenue stream and was marketed with the "Let It Go" short film.</p>

                <p>"Let It Go" has now accumulated over 1.4 million views on YouTube, and has inspired a follow-up "The making of Let It Go" presentation on the same channel.</p>


                ]]>
                </desc>            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/letitgo1.jpg, img/casestudies/letitgo3.jpg, img/casestudies/letitgo4.jpg, img/casestudies/letitgo5.jpg</thumb> 
                <video>img/casestudies/letitgo.mp4</video>
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/letitgo.mp4</main-video>  
                <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=veGbtkyoe_Q</link> 
        </caseStudyItem>  

         <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Pudge Creek - YouTube Video</heading>
                <client>Evokelabs</client>
                <technology>Concept, 3dsmax, Motion, Social Media</technology>
                <brief>Pudge Creek is the Wolf Creek trailer with a digitally replaced 3d character.</brief>
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[<p>Pudge Creek is a digital remake of the Wolf Creek trailer. The idea was to replace John Jarratt's character with a 3d game character for the Dota2 community.</p>

                <p>The work involved creating and rigging a 3d model. Assigning animation controllers and cloth dynamics to the model. Matching the model's animation and lighting to Mick Taylor's. And then compositing these shots into After Effects. There was a total of forty-one 3d effect shots. By the end of it, I had replaced Mick Taylor with Pudge within 1.5 weeks.</p>

                <p>With help of a friend, I had submitted this piece to Twitter, Reddit and other communities who would be interested in seeing this video. Once a few key players and gate-keepers saw the treading video on social sites and shared it, the video exploded into popularity. Within 24 hours, there was 5K views on the trailer.  Within a week, 40K views. This video is now sitting over 100K views.</p>

                ]]>
                </desc>
                <thumb>img/casestudies/pudgecreek1.jpg, img/casestudies/pudgecreek1.gif, img/casestudies/pudgecreek3.jpg, img/casestudies/pudgecreek4.jpg </thumb> 
                <video>img/casestudies/pudgecreek.mp4</video> 
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/pudge.mp4</main-video>  
                <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OGpwAhMmhyk</link>
        </caseStudyItem>  

        <caseStudyItem>
                <heading>AJF Partnership Collection</heading>
                <client>AJF Partnership  &amp; and many accounts</client>
                <technology>Animate CC, After Effects, Front End, HTML, CSS</technology>
                <brief>A collection of banners, videos, edm and other digital works done for AJF Partnership and their clients.</brief>
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[<p>I've been a freelance resource for AJF Partnership between 2013 - 2015. During that time, I've worked on multiple digital campaigns and have filled roles such as flash developer, motion designer, front end developer and eDM developer - as well as being a general digital consultant for them. While the creative directors, account holders and their clients came up with the ideas, I was often hired to produce them when their in-house team was either too busy or too inexperienced for digital work.</p>

                <p>I've done a collection of digital work for AJF Partnership; including banners, videos, email template and front-end development. The clients I've worked for are also plentiful; including News Corp, Helga's Bakehouse, Rams Homeloans, Frangelico, Wild Turkey, Wattyl Paints, Sky Vodka, Donut King, Michel's Patisserie and Mr Men.</p>
                ]]>
                </desc>
                <video>img/casestudies/ajf.mp4</video>        
                <thumb>img/casestudies/ajf1.jpg, img/casestudies/ajf3.jpg,  img/casestudies/ajf4.jpg</thumb>  
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/ajfcollection.mp4</main-video>
                <link></link>
        </caseStudyItem>
    
     
        <!-- <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>My Time Here - Independent CGI Short Film</heading>
                <client>Evoke Labs</client>
                <technology>Concept, 3dsmax, Motion, Sound Design</technology>
                <brief>My Time Here is an independent 11 min short CGI film produced by Evokelabs.</brief>
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[<p>My Time Here is a 11min CGI short film. It contains realistic 3D characters, Hollywood-like original score, professional voiced dialogue and was written by talent within the industry. I always wanted to put the skills and talents I’ve learnt from motion, 3d, as well as advertising into good use and create a short film to tell a unique story.</p>

                <p>This project took two years of on and off work to create. It features three 3d animation characters, facial rigs, lots of different props, lighting rigs, clothing sims, FumeFX for smoke and atmosphere effects, matte paintings and plenty of other digital effects that tested my abilities. I hosted hours worth of personal video lectures on how to create 3d short films for any cgi director who would like to attempt a project like this but don’t know where to start - which ended up being more popular than the actual movie.</p>
                ]]>
                </desc>
                <thumb>
                img/casestudies/mytimehere1.jpg,  img/casestudies/mytimehere2.jpg,  img/casestudies/mytimehere3.jpg, img/casestudies/mytimehere4.jpg
                </thumb> 
                <video>img/casestudies/mytimehere.mp4</video> 
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/mytimehere.mp4</main-video>   
                <link>./works/MyTimeHere/</link>
        </caseStudyItem> -->


        <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Optus Go Places – Motion Design</heading>
                <client>M&amp;C Saatchi &amp; Optus</client>            
                <technology>3dsmax, After Effects CC, Animate CC</technology>            
                <brief>Optus Go Places is glossy video experience shown in Optus dealership stores.</brief>
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[<p>Optus Go Places was an interactive video experience showcased in Optus dealerships stores. Users were encourage to interact with a touchscreen which showcased various 3d motion pieces informing people of the Optus Go Places services.</p>

                <p>These videos were built in After Effect with some elements of 3d brought in from 3dsmax whenever depth was required. There were dozens of motion effects in this 720p hi-def motion design including camera work, masking effects, 3d effects and multiple layers tweens to create an engaging piece of video work.</p>
                ]]>
                </desc>            
                <thumb>img/casestudies/goplaces1.jpg,img/casestudies/goplaces2.jpg,img/casestudies/goplaces3.jpg</thumb>  
                <video>img/casestudies/optusmotion.mp4</video> 
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/optus.mp4</main-video>
                <link></link>
        </caseStudyItem>

        <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>Powerhouse Productions Banners &amp; Minisites</heading>
                <client>Evokelabs &amp; Powerhouse Productions</client>
                <technology>Strategy, UX, Design, Animate, After Effects, AS2</technology>
                <brief>Collection of digital campaigns ranging from banners to minisites for Australian dance event producer.</brief>
                <video>img/casestudies/php.mp4</video>
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/powerhouse.mp4</main-video>  
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[
                <p>Powerhouse Productions was Australia’s largest all-aged dance event producer, and I was responsible for all of their digital marketing campaigns. My client's events are marketed to a youthful and energetic demographic, so I had the opportunity to push my Flash abilities to its creative limits. Most of the flash banners created for these events were built to be eye-catching and unique - using particle effects, layer blendings, and AS2 driven effects.</p>

                <p>In additional to these banners, occasionally a Flash minisite would be built for the next dance event. They were all uniquely designed, mixed with music, informative and encouraged users to buy tickets online. Built using AS2, no minisite was ever created the same - advancing the awareness of the parties that went way beyond the typical flyer.<p>

                <p>Ticket sales usually picked up after these sites were built - leading to their first sell out event at the Acer Arena. It also got my name out there as someone who specialised in doing good work for DJs, promotors and events - earning new clients across Australia and the UK.</p>

                ]]>
                </desc>

                <thumb>img/casestudies/ph1.jpg, img/casestudies/ph2.jpg,img/casestudies/ph3.jpg, img/casestudies/ph4.jpg</thumb>  
                <link></link>
        </caseStudyItem>     

        <!-- <caseStudyItem>
                <heading>Westfield – Motion Builds</heading>
                <client>M&amp;C Saatchi &amp; Westfield</client>
                <technology>After Effects CC, Animate CC </technology>
                <brief>A collection of video builds appearing inside Westfield shopping centres.</brief>
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[<p>Westfield displays visual content on their LCD displays throughout their malls. While at MC Saatchi, I was often responsible for the creation of Westfield media campaigns, converting their briefs and storyboards into published video files, which was then distributed and displayed all across Westfield Australia via oOh! media platforms.</p>

                <p>My experience in traditional motion and animation gave me the opportunity to add exaggeration, secondary movements and various effects that often extended beyond the brief. These would include subtle bounces, tweening exaggerations, tasteful 3d and various motion effects that raised the visual bar. According to the producers, Westfield was impressed with both the quality and the quick turnaround of these video works since I had become their resource.</p>

                <p>Also included in my portfolio is a video pitch presented to Westfield that I created with After Effects. This was used by M&C Saatchi to help present Westfield’s potentially new UX/UI site. It features a breakdown of the divs blocks in 3d space, with interesting camera pannings and walk-throughs of the hierarchical nature of the proposed site.</p>
                ]]>
                </desc>
                <video>img/casestudies/westfield.mp4</video> 
                <main-video>works/westfield/westfieldPitch/Westfieldpitch.mp4</main-video> 
                <thumb>img/casestudies/westfield1.jpg, img/casestudies/westfield2.jpg,img/casestudies/westfield3.jpg</thumb>
                <link>./works/westfield/index.html</link>

        </caseStudyItem> -->
        <caseStudyItem>            
                <heading>GPYR / Y&amp;R ANZ COLLECTION</heading>
                <client>GPYR / Y&amp;R ANZ and many accounts</client>            
                <technology>Art Direction, Flash CC, HTML, CSS, AS2</technology>
                <brief>A collection of digital builds and flash jobs done for GPYR agency.</brief>
                <desc>  
                <![CDATA[<p>Y&R was the first big break in my digital career. GPYR's Head of Digital noticed my Flash portfolio in the golden days of SWF, right where the demand for Flash designers and developers was at its highest. He took a gamble on my digital talents, and I was fortunate enough to be offered a freelance role at GPYR. I worked there for around a year, designing eDMs, coding Flash banner minigames, creating minisites, and even solo created an Australia Idol banner campaign from scratch for a national wide audience. A great experience.</p>]]>
                </desc>
                <video>img/casestudies/15-gpyr.mp4</video>
                <main-video>https://d19s7v0o35zltc.cloudfront.net/gpyr.mp4</main-video>
                <thumb>img/casestudies/gpyr4.jpg, img/casestudies/gpyr2.jpg, img/casestudies/gpyr3.jpg, img/casestudies/gpyr1.jpg</thumb>            
                <link></link>
        </caseStudyItem>            
    
</caseStudy>
